<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Víctor Henriques</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I am Víctor, a guy who shares a great interest in economics and finance. At first glance, one can think it may be difficult to understand the mathematics used on these fields, although I can assure you it is even worse when you spend a great length of time on these matters. I&#39;m not that good in math, nor at statistics, and, quite frankly, sometimes I find myself a little bit lost while studying a given topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, why does someone decide to learn such things? Well, the answer becomes so much easier when one can see what he&#39;s actually doing while starts to use interactive tools to solve real problems in life. As an undergraduate student, I was intrigued by the first time I wrote a regression code on &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; and, since then, I&#39;ve learnt a lot about the &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somehow, life lead me to work as an Economic Researcher. During those years, I&#39;ve had some experience doing macro projections for the &lt;strong&gt;Relatório Focus&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Agência Estado&lt;/strong&gt;, and I took what was best to my knowledge to implement &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; on daily work. Nowadays, I&#39;ve decided to start a Doctoral Program, challenging myself once again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You see, &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; has been a huge part of my professional life so far. In a nutshell, I&#39;d like to share my experience all the way through the Doctoral Program, offering for you the best free available content that one can expected. Also, I&#39;d like to spending some time on a personal project together with &lt;strong&gt;Ricardo Oscar&lt;/strong&gt;. The project called &lt;strong&gt;mineirandodados&lt;/strong&gt; aims working with a fun content, such as sports data analysis, gambling, lottery and everything we don&#39;t have clue after a discussion on a bar drinking a few beers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luis Tavares</title>
      <link>/authors/luis-tavares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/luis-tavares/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricardo de Souza Tavares</title>
      <link>/authors/ricardo-de-souza-tavares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/ricardo-de-souza-tavares/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
