<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Víctor Henriques</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I am Víctor, a guy who shares a great interest on economics and finance. At first glance, one can think it may be difficult to understand the mathematics used on these fields, but I can assure you it is even worse when you spend a great length of time on these matters. I&#39;m not that good in math, nor at statistics, and, quite frankly, sometimes I find myself a little bit lost while studying a given topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, why someone decides to learn such thing? Well, the answer became so much simpler when one can see what he&#39;s actually doing when starts to use interactive tools to solve real problems in life. As an undergraduate economics student, I was intrigued by the first time I wrote a regression code on R. I felt so much joy in the fact that I and since then I have felt so much joy playing with R.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;freshman at Economic Doctoral Program at Fundação Getúlio Vargas. As a freshman, I haven&#39;t start my research yet, althought I am pretty sure what would be. My intentions towards this website is fundamentally 
By the time, I faced a&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I have been spending some time on a personal project together with Ricardo Oscar. The project called &amp;ldquo;mineirandodados&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; aims working with a fun content, such as sports data analysis, gambling, lottery and everything we don&#39;t have clue after drinking a few beers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Average guys like me tends to quit before they try first.
You must have to ask yourself&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.Like in many cases, you ask yourself to not quit without try first/instantaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it is no an excuse to bail out these topics like a little bitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;, although those fields extre. Like the other, I&#39;m not diffenrete&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the time goes, the taught me that we are constantly lead to think on average, but the consequences about it could be catasthophic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;freshman at Economic Doctoral Program at Fundação Getúlio Vargas. As a freshman, I haven&#39;t start my research yet, althought I am pretty sure what would be&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roughly speaking, I intend to and a sports enthisiastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I have been spending some time on a personal project together with Ricardo Oscar. The project called &amp;ldquo;mineirandodados&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; aims working with a fun content, such as sports data analysis, gambling, lottery and everything we don&#39;t have an intuitive knowledge after drink a few beers on a given Bar.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricardo de Souza Tavares</title>
      <link>/authors/ricardo-de-souza-tavares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/ricardo-de-souza-tavares/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
